<quizzes>

  <!-- BEGIN QUIZ: WHAT KIND OF PERSON ARE YOU? -->
  <quiz>
    <title>
      What kind of a person are you?
    </title>
    <description>
      Take this quiz to see what kind of person you REALLY are! Find out once and for all!
    </description>
    <questions>

      <question>
        <title>
          Starving Friends
        </title>
        <text>
          You're eating a sandwich, and your friend is starving.\nWhat do you do?
        </text>
        <answers>
          <answer>
            <text>
              Give your friend half the sandwich, and pat yourself on the back for being an incredible person
            </text>
            <attribute_modifiers>
              ego=+5;empathy=+5;goodness=+5;humor=-10;
            </attribute_modifiers>
          </answer>
          <answer>
            <text>
              Tell your friend life isn't always fair
            </text>
            <attribute_modifiers>
              ego=+2;empathy=-5;goodness=-5;humor=-10;
            </attribute_modifiers>
          </answer>
          <answer>
            <text>
              Start to offer your friend a sandwich, but then pull it away at the last moment and berate him for being too incompetant to feed himself
            </text>
            <attribute_modifiers>
              ego=+5;empathy=-5;goodness=-10;humor=-10;
            </attribute_modifiers>
          </answer>
          <answer>
            <text>
              Slap your friend in the face with your ham sandwich, then continue eating
            </text>
            <attribute_modifiers>
              ego=+5;empathy=-5;goodness=-5;humor=+10;
            </attribute_modifiers>
          </answer>
        </answers>
      </question>



      <question>
        <title>
          The Poor Old Lady
        </title>
        <text>
          You're eating at the park, when suddenly an old lady walking past you, slips and falls on the floor right in front of you. How do you react?
        </text>
        <answers>
          <answer>
            <text>
              Rush to help her! She could be hurt!
            </text>
            <attribute_modifiers>
              ego=-10;empathy=+10;humor=-10;
            </attribute_modifiers>
          </answer>
          <answer>
            <text>
              Realize every living being will one day disappear into the abyss. Then let the darkness consume you as you both laugh and cry uncontrollably.
            </text>
            <attribute_modifiers>
              ego=-20;empathy=-10;humor=-10;
            </attribute_modifiers>
          </answer>
          <answer>
            <text>
              Try to distract her from the pain by also falling down, but in an even more ridiculous way if possible.
            </text>
            <attribute_modifiers>
              ego=-10;empathy=+10;humor=+10;
            </attribute_modifiers>
          </answer>
          <answer>
            <text>
              Realize she probably killed a bunch of ants, and immediately burst into tears.
            </text>
            <attribute_modifiers>
              ego=-10;empathy=+10;humor=-10;
            </attribute_modifiers>
          </answer>
        </answers>
      </question>

      <question>
        <title>Spoiled Milk</title>
        <text>
          You're really hungry and want to pour yourself a nice bowl of cereal. There's only one problem: The milk smells strange.\n\nYou don't want to get a sick stomach, but you can't be sure. What do you do?
        </text>
        <answers>
          <answer>
            <text>
              Use the milk for your cereal and see what happens. You're too hungry to resist, wouldn't want anyone else to get sick.
            </text>
            <attribute_modifiers>
              ego=-10;empathy=+10;humor=-5;
            </attribute_modifiers>
          </answer>
          <answer>
            <text>
              Ask your spouse to come in, and without explaining the situation, instruct them to take a deep breath. If they gag, laugh uncontrollably and throw the milk away.
            </text>
            <attribute_modifiers>
              ego=+5;empathy=-10;humor=+10;
            </attribute_modifiers>
          </answer>
          <answer>
            <text>
              Pour a nice tall glass for your spouse, and wait to see what happens.
            </text>
            <attribute_modifiers>
              ego=+5;empathy=-10;humor=-10;
            </attribute_modifiers>
          </answer>
        </answers>
      </question>

    </questions>

    <characters>

      <character>
        <title>A Piece of Crap</title>
        <description>
          It's likely you enjoy your life, but there is something very wrong with you. You probably gain strength by ruining other people's lives.
        </description>
        <attributes>
          ego=+50;empathy=-50;humor=-50;
        </attributes>
      </character>

      <character>
        <title>Boring</title>
        <description>
          You may be a good person, but will most likely die alone.
        </description>
        <attributes>
          ego=-50;empathy=+50;humor=-50;
        </attributes>
      </character>

      <character>
        <title>Hilarious Waste of Time</title>
        <description>
          People find you hilarious, and you're usually the life of the party. That's why it's so unfortunate that you are most likely throwing your life away on constant trivial shenanigans.
        </description>
        <attributes>
          ego=0;empathy=0;humor=+50;
        </attributes>
      </character>

    </characters>
  </quiz>





</quizzes>
